marathonbet.co.uk 2014-12-03

# MARATHON. Help - Privacy Policy

By agreeing to register with Marathonbet.co.uk you accept our terms and conditions.

## Use of Information

Registration with Marathonbet.co.uk is mandatory if you wish to deposit and bet on this website.

During the registration stage we will ask you for personal information. This will include your name, address, date of birth and contact details, such as your email and telephone number.

We may validate these details and other personal information supplied by you during registration against appropriate third party databases. By accepting these terms and conditions you consent to such checks being made. In performing these checks personal information provided by you may be disclosed to a registered Credit Reference Agency which may keep a record of that information. This check is done only to confirm your identity, no credit check is performed and your credit rating will be unaffected. All information provided by you will be treated securely and strictly in accordance with the pertaining data protection Laws.

You may update your personal information at any time in the My Account/Personal Details section of the website or by telephoning the Customer Care team. We will also ask you to enter a unique identification ID and a password which you will use for any subsequent logins on this website.

As the internet is a global commodity, its use to collect and process information data may involve the transmission of this data on an international basis, including countries outside the European Economic area. Therefore, by registering and using our website, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of your personal data in this way.

We may occasionally wish to contact you by email with information on promotional offers (such as Free bets), technical updates and new site features. If you wish to unsubscribe, please correct the correspondence check boxes on the the My Account/Other Settings page accordingly. Alternatively, this can be done by contacting Customer Care. You may also select the “Click this link to unsubscribe” option at the foot of any promotional email that you may receive from us to prevent any future promotional marketing being sent to you via email.

## Cookies

When using the website a cookie will be stored. A cookie is a small piece of data used by your browser which is stored on your computer for a period of time. Every time you log into your account, a cookie will be created and stored. Once you log out, the cookie will be destroyed.

If you would like to find out more about cookies, please visit: <http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/>

## Security

This website has been designed to provide the best levels of security to the customer. All critical communications between you and the website are encrypted using 256 bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

When you log in, we recognize your IP address. This is then recorded on our system. When you log in again, you can see your last log-in date and the IP address used. This is done to assist you in preventing unauthorised access to your account.

There are also a number of additional security measures in place to protect the confidentiality and integrity of your information. Our servers have installed the latest firewall technology to act as a solid barrier to prevent unauthorised access.

## Communications

In the interest of all customers Marathonbet shall record all telephone calls and internet communications with customers for training, dispute resolution and security purposes. When a dispute occurs which cannot be resolved by Marathonbet, the relevant recording(s) may be made available to arbitrators or authorities.

## Disclosure

The company have a legal duty to protect your information under the Data Protection Act 1998 (UK legislation), (Bailiwick of Guernsey) Law 2001 and EU privacy and the OECD Guidelines on the Protection of Privacy and Transborder Data Flow of Personal Data. We are obliged to provide information requested by our regulating authorities.

## Other Sites

Our web site contains links to other sites. The company have no influence over other sites privacy policies, and as such have no responsibility for any information you may enter when accessing one of these links.

The company reserves the right to amend this privacy policy at any time.

## Queries

Should you have any queries about the use of information under this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

**Email**

**Post**

141 Davigdor Road  
Hove  
BN3 1RE  
United Kingdom

**Phone**

From the UK: Freephone 0800 9757882

Outside the UK: +44 1273 964705

Last Modified Date: 30/06/14
